If you think you know Family Guy, you don’t know Sith.
Family Guy Presents: Blue Harvest is a animation, comedy,
science fiction film directed by Dominic Polcino.
With the Griffins stuck at home during a blackout, Peter tells
the story of "Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope".
Peter Griffin as Han Solo / Brian Griffin as Chewbacca / Stewie Griffin as Darth Vader / Glenn Quagmire as C-3PO / Tom Tucker as Imperial
Newscaster / Carter Pewterschmidt as Uncle Owen / Safeguard #1 / Italian #2 / White Guard #2 (voice), played by Seth MacFarlane.
Lois Griffin as Princess Leia / Barbara Pewterschmidt as
Aunt Beru (voice), played by Alex Borstein.
Chris Griffin as Luke Skywalker (voice), played by Seth Green.
Meg Griffin (voice), played by Mila Kunis.
Cleveland Brown as R2-D2 / John Herbert as Obi-Wan Kenobi / Bruce the Performance
Artist as Greedo / Fouad as Imperial Officer (voice), played by Mike Henry.
Diane Simmons as Imperial Newscaster (voice), played by Lori Alan.
"Blue Harvest" is the season premiere of the sixth season of the American animated television
series Family Guy, and the first part of the series' Laugh It Up, Fuzzball trilogy.
It originally aired on Fox in the United States on September 23, 2007.
The episode is a retelling and parody of the 1977 blockbuster film Star Wars, recasting the show's characters as Star Wars
characters, created with permission from Lucasfilm on the condition that the characters look exactly as they do in the movies.
The plot follows Peter as he retells the story of Star Wars
while the electricity is out in their house.
The title is a reference to the working title of Return of the Jedi.
The episode was written by Alec Sulkin and directed by Dominic Polcino, and guest-stars
Chevy Chase, Beverly D'Angelo, Mick Hucknall, Rush Limbaugh, and Judd Nelson.
The episode also includes recurring voice actors Lori Alan, Adam West, Ralph Garman, Danny Smith, John Viener, Steve
Callaghan, Kirker Butler, Mark Hentemann, Johnny Brennan, Jon Benjamin, Phil LaMarr, and Wally Wingert.
It was viewed by 10.86 million viewers on its original broadcast.
The film explores themes of dark comedy, satire, parody, crude humor.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.